
day_one_questions = [{
    "question": "Which is not a data type?",
    "answers": {
        "a": "Boolean",
        "b": "Floating Point",
        "c": "Variable",
    },
    "correctAnswer": "c",
}, {
    "question": "What is a correct syntax to output 'Hello World' in Python??",
    "answers": {
        "a": "echo 'Hello World",
        "b": "p('Hello World')",
        "c": "print('Hello World')",
    },
    "correctAnswer": "c",
}, {
    "question": "How do you insert comments in Python?",
    "answers": {
        "a": "#This is a comment",
        "b": "//This is a comment",
        "c": "/*This is a comment*/",
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a",
}, {
    "question": "What is the correct file extension for Python?",
    "answers": {
        "a": ".pyth",
        "b": ".py",
        "c": ".pyt",
    },
    "correctAnswer": "b",
}, {
    "question": "What do we call the associated data of our data?",
    "answers": {
        "a": "Properties",
        "b": "Methods",
        "c": "Booleans",
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a",
}, {
    "question": "What type of data will the .len() method return?",
    "answers": {
        "a": "Boolean",
        "b": "String",
        "c": "Integer",
    },
    "correctAnswer": "c",
}, {
    "question": "What integer would you pass in square brackets to find the first character of a String",
    "answers": {
        "a": "[0]",
        "b": "[-1]",
        "c": "[1]",
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a",
}, {
    "question": "What do we call the built in functions used to manipulate data?",
    "answers": {
        "a": "Properties",
        "b": "Methods",
        "c": "upper()",
    },
    "correctAnswer": "b",
}, {
    "question": "What is the name of the convention we use to execute methods on our data?",
    "answers": {
        "a": "Dot Notation",
        "b": "py runfile.py",
        "c": "Floating Points",
    },
    "correctAnswer": "a",
}, {
    "question": "Where should we import libraries generally in our python file?",
    "answers": {
        "a": "Before the method call",
        "b": "At the End",
        "c": "At the Top",
    },
    "correctAnswer": "c",
}]
